David Gertsch

Partner at Elevate Practices and HGG Advisors

Summary

Experienced Finance with a demonstrated history of working in the dental accounting industry. Skilled in cloud based accounting, financial statements, small business entity structuring, and tax. Strong finance professional with a MAcc from Southern Utah University.

Experience

Partner at HGG Advisors

October 2015 - Present

Finance at Elevate Practices

October 2015 - Present

Audit Manager at HintonBurdick CPAs & Advisors

January 2014 - October 2015 (1 year 10 months)

Audit Manager at Deloitte & Touche

September 2008 - January 2014 (5 years 5 months)

Education

Southern Utah University

MAcc, Accounting, 2003 - 2008

Wasatch high school

1997 - 2001

David Gertsch

Partner at Elevate Practices and HGG Advisors



Contact David on LinkedIn